Your father. Your father. Your?
Father is a bitch
...
आज ले ता पोले को गोराने ता। लावा ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता ले ता
In this program we are going to run this model.
Speak into the computer and your my computer is gonna give me
My computer is going to give me the real my computer
is going to give me the real answers to all my questions. That's pretty cool.
Ha! You got ignored.
Lohila, Chinna Nagaratimi
timi chintanagarana hai? timi chintanagarana timi sappai kaam mundsa.
tím liram bru jaggir pãoso tím icintanau kar
i will make it in my stream.
نمویدی از این از این ایشنیشن نمتیش این ایشنیشن کاریگا از فرنم بودی از این بودی
너희랑 지금 왜 이래?
Hello, get your hot cover. If I get a language for you.
आपना दाम आगा
ان்டா کیا جانے மசுக்கச் சவாது